export const data = [
  //Q1
  {
    question: "Who said 'Say that to me again and I'll cut your face off'?",
    option1: 'Andy',
    option2: 'Dwight',
    option3: 'Erin',
    option4: 'Rolf',
    answer: 3
  },
  //Q2
  {
    question: "How old is Pam when she marries Jim?",
    option1: "28",
    option2: "31",
    option3: "26",
    option4:"30",
    answer: 4
  },
  //Q3
  {
    question: "What is Michael Scott's zodiac sign?",
    option1: "Cancer",
    option2: "Pisces",
    option3: "Taurus",
    option4: "Sagittarius",
    answer: 2
  },
  //Q4
  {
    question: "What kind of bear is best?",
    option1: "Black bear",
    option2: "Grizzly bear",
    option3: "That is a ridiculous question",
    option4: "Polar bear",
    answer: 3
  },
  //Q5
  {
    question: "Who does Michael award 'Hottest in the Office' at the 8th annual Dundie Awards?",
    option1: "Ryan",
    option2: "Jim",
    option3: "Pam",
    option4: "Hollie",
    answer: 1
  }, 
  //Q6
  {
    question: "In 'The Alliance' episode, what color does Angela say is whore-ish?",
    option1: "Green",
    option2: "Red",
    option3: "Yellow",
    option4: "Orange",
    answer: 1
  },
  //Q7
  {
    question: "What is Michael's middle name?",
    option1: "Jerry",
    option2: "Kurt",
    option3: "Gary",
    option4: "Steven",
    answer: 3
  },
  //Q8
  {
    question: "In the pilot episode, how many years does Michael Scott say he has worked at Dunder Mifflin?",
    option1: "13",
    option2: "15",
    option3: "11",
    option4: "12",
    answer: 4
  },
  //Q9
  {
    question:"What is Gabe's middle name?",
    option1: "Nancy",
    option2: "Susan",
    option3: "Linda",
    option4: "Debbie",
    answer: 2
  },
  //Q10
  {
    question: "What color is Angela's cat, Bandit?",
    option1: "Black",
    option2: "White",
    option3: "Orange",
    option4: "Calico",
    answer: 4
  },
  //Q11
  {
    question: "Ryan caused a fire in the office by heating up what food item?",
    option1: "A cheese pita",
    option2: "A personal pizza",
    option3: "A panini sandwhich",
    option4: "A pepperoni pizza",
    answer: 1
  },
  //Q12
  {
    question: "What item does Dwight keep in his car for special occasions?",
    option1: "Nunchucks",
    option2: "Beet juice",
    option3: "Birkenstocks",
    option4: "Throwing stars",
    answer: 3
  },
  //Q13
  {
    question: "Which Harry Potter book did Dwight say he would bring to a deserted island",
    option1: "Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban",
    option2: "Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets",
    option3: "Harry Potter and the Sorcerer's Stone",
    option4: "Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire",
    answer: 1
  },
  //Q14
  {
    question: "What is Michael Scott's online dating username?",
    option1: "Michael Scarn",
    option2: "Little kid lover",
    option3: "Little kid friend",
    option4: "Michael Scotch",
    answer: 2
  },
  //Q15
  {
    question: "Which The Office actor helped co-produce season 9?",
    option1: "Ed Helms",
    option2: "John Krasinski",
    option3: "Leslie David Baker",
    option4: "Phyllis Smith",
    answer: 2
  },
  //Q16
  {
    question: "Which actor auditioned for the role of Jim Halpert?",
    option1: "Benjamin Bratt",
    option2: "Justin Long",
    option3: "Adam Scott",
    option4: "Seth Rogan",
    answer: 3
  },
  //Q17
  {
    question: "To what company does the cast and crew of The Office owe their success?",
    option1: "RIM (Research in Motion)",
    option2: "Apple",
    option3: "YouTube",
    option4: "Facebook",
    answer: 2
  },
  //Q18
  {
    question: "What was the original reason a documentary crew started filming Dunder Mifflin?",
    option1: "To show the unconventional managing style of Michael Scott",
    option2: "To show how office romances change coworker dynamics",
    option3: "To show how workplace friendships develop and blossom",
    option4: "To show how the office was dealing with suicide",
    answer: 4
  },
  //Q19
  {
    question: "How much did the proposal scene between Jim and Pam cost?",
    option1: "$75,000",
    option2: "$300,000",
    option3: "$250,000",
    option4: "$100,000",
    answer: 3
  },
  //Q20
  {
    question: "Steve Carell's role at Dwight and Angela's wedding was a secret to the cast and crew, during table readings which character read his lines?",
    option1: "Creed",
    option2: "Mose",
    option3: "Robert California",
    option4: "Ryan",
    answer: 1
  }
];
